var questions=[{
  "question":"Which of the following will directly stop the execution of a Thread? ",
  "option1":"wait()",
  "option2" :"notify()",
  "option3"	:"notifyall()",
  "option4"	:"exits synchronized code",
  "answer":"1"
},{
	"question":"Which arithmetic operations can result in the throwing of an ArithmeticException?",
"option1"	:"/ , %",
"option2"	:"* , +",
	"option3":"! , -",
	"option4":">>, <<",
	"answer":"1"
	
},{
"question":"Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
	"option1":"string",
   "option2" :"String",
   "option3" :"myString",
	"option4":"txt",
	"answer":"2"
},{
	"question":"What allows the programmer to destroy an object x?",
	"option1":"x.delete()",	
	"option2":"x.finalize()",
	"option3":"Runtime.getRuntime().gc()",	
	"option4":"Only the garbage collection system can destroy an object",
	"answer":"4"
},{
	"question":"Which statement is true? ",

	"option1":"All objects that are eligible for garbage collection will be garbage collected by the garbage collector",
	"option2":"Objects with at least one reference will never be garbage collected.",
	"option3":"Objects from a class with the finalize() method overridden will never be garbage collected.",
	"option4":"Objects instantiated within anonymous inner classes are placed in the garbage collectible heap",
"answer":"4"
},{   
     "question":"Which is true about an anonymous inner class? ",
"option1"	:"It can extend exactly one class and implement exactly one interface.",
"option2"	:"It can extend exactly one class and can implement multiple interfaces.",
  "option3" :"It can extend exactly one class or implement exactly one interface.",
   "option4":"It can implement multiple interfaces regardless of whether it also extends a class.",
   "answer":"4"
},{
"question"	:"What is the name of the method used to start a thread execution? ",
		"option1":"init();",
    "option2":"start();",
	"option3":"run();",
	"option4":"resume();",
	"answer":"2"
},{
	"question":"Which of these can be used to fully abstract a class from its implementation?",
	"option1":"Objects",
	"option2":"Packages",
	"option3":"Interfaces.",
	"option4":"None of the Mentioned",

	"answer":"3"
	
},{
	"question":"Which of the following stops execution of a thread? ",
 "option1":"Calling SetPriority() method on a Thread object",
 "option2":"Calling notify() method on an object",
 "option3":"Calling wait() method on an object",
"option4":" Calling read() method on an InputStream object",
"answer":"2"
	
},{
"question"	:"How many arguments can be passed to main()?",
 "option1":"Infinite",
 "option2":"Only 1",
 "option3":"System Dependent",
 "option4":"None of the mentioned",
 "answer":"1"
},{
"question":"Which of the following is a correct constructor for thread? ",
 "option1":"Thread(Runnable a, String str)",
 "option2":"Thread(int priority)",
 "option3":"Thread(Runnable a, int priority)",
"option4" :"Thread(Runnable a, ThreadGroup t)",
"answer":"1"
},{
	
"question":"Which of these data types is used to store command line arguments? ",
"option1":"Array",
 "option2":"Stack",
 "option3":"String",
 "option4":"Integer",
"answer":"3"
},{
	"question":"When Overloading does not occur? ",
 "option1":"More than one method with same name but different method signature and different number or type of parameters",
"option2" :"More than one method with same name, same signature but different number of signature",
 "option3":"More than one method with same name, same signature, same number of parameters but different type",
 "option4":"More than one method with same name, same number of parameters and type but different signature",
"answer":"4"
	
},{	
"question":"Which of these keywords is used by a class to use an interface defined previously? ",
 "option1":"import ",
 "option2":"Import",
 "option3":"implements",
 "option4":"Implements",
 "answer":"3"
},{
"question":"Which of the following classes can catch all exceptions which cannot be caught? ",
 "option1":"RuntimeException ",
"option2" :"Error",
 "option3":"Exception",
 "option4":"ParentException",
"answer":"2"	
}]